Mediated,
oh oh The city quiet, the sun is down We're in the
glow of the other side of town The beat is calling
from a place I know Just follow the sound We're
dancing in the neon We're moving to the night is
gone Forget about tomorrow We're shining like a
light Dancing in the neon tonight
Dancing in the neon tonight
The rhythm's heavy A flashing bright reflected
colors in your eyes I don't care what the real
world wants This moment's all that I could ever
want We're dancing in the neon We're moving till
the night is gone Forget about tomorrow We're
shining like a light Dancing in the neon tonight
Don't stop, don't stop the feelin' This music's
got me reelin' Don't stop, don't stop the beat
The beat, beat, beat, beat, beat, beat, beat,
beat, beat, beat, beat, beat, beat, beat, beat,
beat, beat, beat We're dancing in the neons.
We're moving till the night is gone. Forget
about tomorrow. We're shining like a light.
Dancing in the neons tonight. Dancing in the
neons.
So the night is gone